It's six o'clock in the morning,
此时是清晨六点
pitch black outside.
外面一片漆黑
My 14-year-old son is fast asleep in his bed,
我十四岁的儿子还在床上熟睡
sleeping the reckless, deep sleep of a teenager.
就像所有十多岁的孩子一样 睡得又香又沉
I flip on the light and physically shake the poor boy awake,
我打开灯 用力把这可怜的男孩摇醒
because I know that, like ripping off a Band-Aid,
因为我清楚 这就像撕创可贴一样
it's better to get it over with quickly.
这事越快越好
I have a friend who yells "Fire!" just to rouse her sleeping teen.
我有个朋友会大叫"着火了"
And another who got so fed up
另一个朋友都已经忍不可忍了
that she had to dump cold water on her son's head
最后不得不往她儿子头上浇冷水
just to get him out of bed.
就为了叫他起床
Sound brutal ...
听起来很残忍...
but perhaps familiar?
但是可能也很熟悉吧
Every morning I ask myself,
每天早上我都扪心自问
"How can I --
"我怎么能...
knowing what I know
具备专业知识
and doing what I do for a living --
靠这个赚钱...
be doing this to my own son?"
却对我自己的儿子做出这种事来"
You see,
大家看
I'm a sleep researcher.
我是个睡眠研究人员
So I know far too much about sleep
所以我非常了解睡眠
and the consequences of sleep loss.
也知道缺乏睡眠的后果
I know that I'm depriving my son of the sleep he desperately needs
我知道自己正在剥夺儿子的睡眠
I also know that by waking him up
我也知道
hours before his natural biological clock tells him he's ready,
在他的自然生物钟告诉他可以起床前叫醒他
I'm literally robbing him of his dreams --
我实际上是剥夺了他的梦...
the type of sleep most associated with learning, memory consolidation
这是睡眠中
and emotional processing.
联系最紧密的部分
But it's not just my kid that's being deprived of sleep.
但不只是我的孩子被剥夺了睡眠
Sleep deprivation among American teenagers is an epidemic.
睡眠剥夺在美国青少年中非常普遍
Only about one in 10 gets the eight to 10 hours of sleep per night
只有大约十分之一的孩子
recommended by sleep scientists and pediatricians.
也就是睡眠专家和儿科医生推荐的睡眠量
Now, if you're thinking to yourself,
如果此刻你心说
"Phew, we're doing good, my kid's getting eight hours,"
"我们还不错 我们的孩子能睡够八小时"
remember,
请记住
eight hours is the minimum recommendation.
八小时是推荐量的最低限度
You're barely passing.
你只是刚刚及格而已
Eight hours is kind of like getting a C on your report card.
八小时就像是考试得了六十分
There are many factors contributing to this epidemic,
造成这种普遍现象有很多因素
but a major factor preventing teens from getting the sleep they need
不过让青少年们睡不够需要的时间
is actually a matter of public policy.
其实是跟一项公共政策有关
Not hormones, social lives or Snapchat.
而不是荷尔蒙 社交生活或是图片分享软件
Across the country,
纵观全国
many schools are starting around 7:30am or earlier,
许多学校上课的时间是早上七点半 甚至更早
despite the fact that major medical organizations recommend
尽管几个主要的医学组织都建议
that middle and high school start no earlier than 8:30am.
初中和高中的上课时间不要在早上八点半以前
These early start policies have a direct effect on how much --
这很早就开始上课的政策直接导致了
or really how little sleep American teenagers are getting.
美国青少年获得的睡眠时间实际上很少
They're also pitting teenagers and their parents
这种政策也让青少年及其父母们
in a fundamentally unwinnable fight against their own bodies.
陷入了一场与身体做对而绝对赢不了的战争
Around the time of puberty,
在青春期
teenagers experience a delay in their biological clock,
青少年的生物钟会发生延迟
which determines when we feel most awake and when we feel most sleepy.
生物钟决定了
This is driven in part by a shift in the release of the hormone melatonin.
这个现象的部分驱动因素是褪黑激素的释放
Teenagers' bodies wait to start releasing melatonin until around 11pm,
青少年的身体
which is two hours later than what we see in adults or younger children.
比成年人或儿童晚了两小时
This means that waking a teenager up at 6am is the biological equivalent
也就是说
of waking an adult up at 4am.
相当于在早上四点叫醒成人
On the unfortunate days when I have to wake up at 4am,
偶尔有些倒霉日子 我必须早上四点起床
I'm a zombie.
那一整天我都是行尸走肉
Functionally useless.
身体机能完全失效
I can't think straight,
我无法清晰地思考
I'm irritable,
我暴躁易怒
and I probably shouldn't be driving a car.
或许还不该开车
But this is how many American teenagers feel every single school day.
但这就是许多美国青少年每一天都体验的
In fact, many of the, shall we say,
事实上 这么说吧
unpleasant characteristics that we chalk up to being a teenager --
有许多我们归咎于青春期的
moodiness, irritability, laziness, depression --
例如喜怒无常 暴躁 懒惰 郁郁寡欢...
could be a product of chronic sleep deprivation.
可能都是慢性睡眠剥夺的结果
For many teens battling chronic sleep loss,
对于很多要对抗慢性睡眠剥夺的青少年来说
their go-to strategy to compensate is consuming large quantities of caffeine
他们首选的弥补措施
in the form of venti frappuccinos,
喝超大杯的星冰乐
or energy drinks and shots.
或是能量饮料和鸡尾酒
So essentially,
所以基本上
we've got an entire population of tired but wired youth.
全美的年轻人都处于即疲倦又兴奋的状态
Advocates of sleep-friendly start times know
主张上课时间晚一点 让孩子多睡会的人知道
that adolescence is a period of dramatic brain development,
青春期是大脑急剧发育的时期
particularly in the parts of the brain
特别是对于脑部
that are responsible for those higher order thinking processes,
与更高层次思维过程有关的部分
including reasoning, problem-solving and good judgment.
包括推理 解决问题和良好的判断力
In other words, the very type of brain activity that's responsible
换句话说
for reining in those impulsive and often risky behaviors
控制那些冲动而且常常是危险的行为
that are so characteristic of adolescence
而这些行为都是
and that are so terrifying to us parents of teenagers.
让我们家长和青少年们害怕的青春期特点
They know that like the rest of us,
他们跟我们一样都知道
when teenagers don't get the sleep they need,
一旦青少年得不到足够的睡眠
their brains, their bodies and behaviors suffer
他们的大脑 身体和行为
with both immediate and lasting effects.
都会受到短期和长期的影响
They can't concentrate,
他们会无法专心
their attention plummets
注意力会大幅下降
and many will even show behavioral signs that mimic ADHD.
很多人甚至会出现类似注意力缺陷多动症的行为
But the consequences of teen sleep loss go well beyond the classroom,
但是青少年睡眠缺失的影响还远不止在课堂上
sadly contributing to many of the mental health problems
令人痛心的是 还会导致青春期
that skyrocket during adolescence,
飙升的心理健康问题
including substance use,
包括药物滥用
depression and suicide.
抑郁和自杀
In our work with teens from LA Unified School District,
我们在洛杉矶联合校区研究青少年时发现
we found that teens with sleep problems
存在睡眠障碍的青少年
were 55 percent more likely to have used alcohol in the past month.
在前一个月里
In another study with over 30,000 high school students,
另外一项对三万多名高中生的研究发现
they found that for each hour of lost sleep,
每缺失一个小时的睡眠
there was a 38 percent increase in feeling sad or hopeless,
感到伤心和绝望的概率就会上升百分之三十八
and a 58 percent increase in teen suicide attempts.
青少年试图自杀的概率则会上升百分之五十八
And if that's not enough,
如果这些数据还不足以说明问题
teens who skip out on sleep are at increased risk
缺乏睡眠的青少年出现困扰全美的
for a host of physical health problems that plague our country,
大量身体健康问题的风险会增加
including obesity, heart disease and diabetes.
包括肥胖 心脏病和糖尿病
Then there's the risk of putting a sleep-deprived teen,
另外 如果让一个刚拿到的驾照
with a newly minted driver's license,
而睡眠被剥夺的青少年开车
behind the wheel.
是很危险的
Studies have shown that getting five hours or less of sleep per night
研究显示
is the equivalent of driving with a blood alcohol content above the legal limit.
还要开车的话
Advocates of sleep-friendly start times,
主张上课时间晚一点 让孩子多睡一会的人
and researchers in this area,
以及这个领域的科研人员
have produced tremendous science
获得了大量的科研数据
showing the tremendous benefits of later start times.
证明了推迟上课时间的巨大好处
The findings are unequivocal,
这些结果是非常明确的
and as a sleep scientist,
作为一名睡眠科学家
I rarely get to speak with that kind of certainty.
我很少会说得这么肯定
Teens from districts with later start times get more sleep.
在有些上课时间比较晚的地区
To the naysayers who may think that if schools start later,
唱反调的人可能会认为 如果上课时间推迟了
teens will just stay up later,
只不过会让青少年们熬夜
the truth is,
事实上
their bedtimes stay the same,
他们就寝的时间会保持不变
but their wake-up times get extended,
但他们起床的时间则延迟了
resulting in more sleep.
因此得到了更多睡眠
They're more likely to show up for school;
他们更愿意去上学
school absences dropped by 25 percent in one district.
在一个地区 缺课率下降了百分之二十五
And they're less likely to drop out.
而且他们更不容易辍学
Not surprisingly, they do better academically.
毫无意外 他们的学习成绩也更好
So this has real implications for reducing the achievement gap.
对缩小成绩差距有真正的影响
Standardized test scores in math and reading
数学和阅读的标准化考试分数
go up by two to three percentage points.
提高了二到三个百分点
That's as powerful as reducing class sizes by one-third fewer students,
这个效果相当于
or replacing a so-so teacher in the classroom
或是把班上一个教学水平一般的老师
with a truly outstanding one.
换成一个教学水平很高的老师
Their mental and physical health improves,
青少年们的身心健康都得到了提高
and even their families are happier.
甚至就连他们的家人都感到更加快乐
I mean, who wouldn't enjoy a little more pleasantness from our teens,
谁不愿意
and a little less crankiness?
少感受点古怪
Even their communities are safer
就连他们所在的社区都更为安全
because car crash rates go down --
因为车祸发生率下降了...
a 70 percent reduction in one district.
一个地区就下降了百分之七十
Given these tremendous benefits,
听了这么多好处
you might think,
大家可能会想
well, this is a no-brainer, right?
这不是很简单的事吗
So why have we as a society failed to heed this call?
那为什么我们的社会却没有这样做呢
Often the argument against later start times goes something like this:
反对推迟上课时间的论点通常是这样的
"Why should we delay start times for teenagers?
"为什么我们要推迟青少年上课的时间
We need to toughen them up so they're ready for the real world!"
我们要劳其筋骨 让他们准备好应对真实世界"
But that's like saying to the parent of a two-year-old,
但这就好像对一个两岁宝宝的家长说
"Don't let Johnny nap,
"不要让小约翰睡午觉
or he won't be ready for kindergarten."
否则他没法准备好上幼儿园"
Delaying start times also presents many logistical challenges.
推迟上课时间还存在很多统筹方面的难题
Not just for students and their families,
不仅是对学生和家长来说
but for communities as a whole.
还包括整个社区
Updating bus routes,
要更新公交线路的安排
increased transportation costs,
会增加交通成本
impact on sports,
对运动项目的影响
care before or after school.
上学前和放学后的照料工作
These are the same concerns that come up in district after district,
在讨论上课时间的时候
time and again around the country
一个地区接一个地区
as school start times are debated.
一再出现同样的担心
And they're legitimate concerns,
这些都是合理的担心
but these are problems we have to work through.
不过这些都是我们必须解决的问题
They are not valid excuses
这些都不是
for failing to do the right thing for our children,
不能对我们的孩子采取正确措施的充分理由
which is to start middle and high schools no earlier than 8:30am.
即让初中和高中上课时间不要在早上八点半之前
And in districts around the country,
在美国 各个已经做出这个改变的地区
big and small, who have made this change,
无论地区大小
they found that these fears are often unfounded
都发现这些担心都是杞人忧天
and far outweighed by the tremendous benefits for student health
而这样的改变对学生健康 成绩和集体公共安全
and performance,
所带来的巨大好处
and our collective public safety.
已经远远值回改变的付出了
So tomorrow morning,
因此 明天早上
when coincidentally we get to set our clocks back by an hour
如果我们碰巧把时钟往后拨了一个小时
and you get that delicious extra hour of sleep,
大家都甜蜜地多睡了一个小时
and the day seems a little longer,
这一天变得长了一点
and a little more full of hope,
更加充满了希望
think about the tremendous power of sleep.
想想睡眠的巨大力量
And think about what a gift it would be
再想想 对我们的孩子来说
for our children to be able to wake up naturally,
能睡到自然醒 与自己的生物钟协调一致
in harmony with their own biology.
是件多么美妙的事
Thank you,
谢谢
and pleasant dreams.
祝大家好梦